It's like when I
was 15 years old
like I went on
a and me and
my friends were on
this beach And for
some reason we decided
to the on the
Like I don't know
I was 15 Anyways
we put a bunch
of into this And
like oh we've caught
so many crabs What
are we going to
do now We're like
okay well let's just
take it back to
the Okay great idea
15 year old Kylie
So we go back
to this hotel and
we're like oh yeah
now we brought the
crabs back to What
do we do We're
like okay let's just
put it in a
Okay let's put the
in a That night
every crab started
breaking each other apart
They killed each other
in that tub Such
a dark story okay
It is the most
gruesome thing I've done
at 15 I'm like
and then we were
like hey let's get
them out Let's put
them back on the
beach Like what the
heck's going on And
they just they kill
each other in that
tub And I was
really sad right I
mean maybe that's why
I've been a vegan
for nine years I
don't know right But
it's like it was
just like horrible to
watch And I always
wondered like why did
the kill each other
So I think that
like I just don't
want us to each
other You we're in
a bucket right now
We're in this tub
And like this it's
not like new water
new nutrients It's not
like an abundant ocean
our echo chamber or
whatever We're in this
echo chamber tub